I have the invocation by Kate Bowman Hearton.
Let us pray.
Heavenly Father, in you, we live and move and have our being.
We humbly pray, you so to guide and govern us by your Holy Spirit,
that in all the cares and occupations of our life,
we may not forget you, but may remember that we are ever walking in your sight
through Jesus Christ our Lord.
Amen.
I pledge allegiance to the flag of the United States of America
and to the root of the Holy Spirit, which stands,
one nation under God in the name of Jesus Christ.
Hey, I have a number four public input and it's given personal experiences.
We have none.
So, I have a number five action items.
Claims.
Make motion.
Second.
Jones.
Hi.
Porter.
Parker.
Hi.
I have a number six.
Action item.
Minutes from the May 20th, 2025 regular session.
May 27th, 2025 regular session.
And June 3rd, 2025 regular session.
Make motion.
Second.
Jones.
Third.
Hi.
Parker.
He's dead.
Hi.
I have a number eight.
Action item.
Claims.
Claim.
F Kate.
F Kate.'s.
Claims.
We have that.
Town Garden.
Lлектa.
Five hundred.
If both of these are approved, then we will have 132,562 dollars and five cents for their
remainder of the year.
I'm going to approve.
Second, Jones, I'm far inside, far first, east at, now I'm number eight, action out of
Tetra Tech, Clay Pinsicola, GRDA, relaxing seeing the amount of 4,845 dollars.
So this is for the modeling, you know Tetra Tech, because of the modeling and everything.
So.
I'm going to ask you a question every second.
Jones, I'm far first, east at, high.
Action out of number nine, resolution MSUA 2025-04 establishing budget amendment for authority
for fiscal year 2526.
So the council did something different at the end of the year.
last meeting on the third of June, and they gave some budget amendment authority authority
to the city manager. There's a cap of $20,000, and what that means, there's adjustments
and there's amendments. So we have 30 funds, those are essentially businesses, 30 businesses,
and the city manager has the authority to transfer money in the past, had money to transfer
inside of a fund. Well, the council went a step further and gave him the authority to transfer money
between funds up to $20,000, and, or, to increase the budget. So if you approved $100,000,
$100,000,000 budget, and we got a $20,000 grant, he could approve that grant. The stipulation
is that he has to report that at the next meeting. Well, while I was kind of setting this step up,
I started thinking, oh my gosh, all of our governing bodies need to approve this authority resolution,
in the authority resolution. So I'm taking it to every trust we have, and the 501c3 senior
center that I'm asking for your approval of this resolution. So it has the exact same language from
the council's resolution. Any questions?
I'm Parker.
Hi. I'm 10. Outside organizational contract provides services for fiscal year 2526. Can you
cross the center? I'm an area economic development service.
You saw this resolution last year. It goes in conjunction with the contracts that the council was
going to consider, or some, well, I consider as an outsider work. This is forward 80, 20 split
of utility credits. Boys and girls club, that is by contract.
I'm not a contract, but I'm in so I'm put in here with a question.
It was a real problem. It's $10,000.
Up to 15,000 and 14 first avenue northeast and tracked A, which I'm assuming is going to be the,
is the gym. I use a community crisis center 21,000 at one location and made up to 13,000
location. And that's based on your average.
See that question again.
I'm sorry, these are the contracts and before you go down to the script, you're going to
put in a piece of plastic in that chair.
We got kind of considered tentatively to the apartment for some longer hours.
That didn't get completed.
So I found that it was in there, so I checked it right back out.
So that's the contract list.
It's the same contract as last year.
And again, grand gate weren't in the hospital.
No, because it doesn't matter.
So this would be for student crisis in our committee's hands.
I'm sorry.
And this is the contract.
This is just community crisis center in late.
So this isn't the word, but right.
You know, that's the word.
Number 10.
It'll be on both agendas.
We're on MSUA and December 10.
So sorry.
So we added the money to the actual contract.
And there's a resolution.
What you want to do.
So you'll see this exact set now.
Everybody will come here.
I mean, the BA kind of talks about the breakdown of the cash versus utility credit.
I think that was kind of.
These are still currently annual contracts.
Right.
Yeah.
Do we have anything.
Any compensation that matter about terms on anything like this.
We write it in the same operating procedure for the website.
We write it in that one time.
And we have this.
We've already got 26.
And then it will apply to 12.
So you know the thought is well, I have so much money so it's like how do we want to best
Did you have this money so I kind of like that day, you know, I mean that way
The board's not the bad guy. I said he's staff's not the bad guy. You know, it's like we have these rules that we follow and I mean
Moving forward to
I'm 11 resolution MSU-82525-105
Approving and adopting the fiscal year 2025 26 utility credit for the boys and girls club of Ottawa County
The Miami Area Economic Development Service and the Community Crisis Center of Oklahoma
Any questions?
Second.
James Lawrence, aye.
Parker.
Aye.
Thank you.
Thank you, Jill.
Uh, 12.
Tinch a lot.
Um, any other new business that we may have ever risen since the posting of this agenda?
I have none.
13 staff reports.
14 trustee community announcements.
15 trust manager communications.
Yes, I just have one thing.
I asked to go in the minutes.
Um, we just, and it's a part of our permit.
So we recently received our permit from DEQ for our water treatment plan.
Upgrade.
So we'll be putting that out for a bit here and before long.
So we just have to put it in a, it has to go on that record that we received it in the minutes.
So just let anybody know.
Thank you, Tyler.
Thank you.
I'm 16 adjournment.
Second.
Parker.
Four.
Five.
Two.